goldbar.net 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy | EM13.com

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Goldbar Enterprises, LLC (“Goldbar.net”). Because Goldbar.net wants to demonstrate its firm commitment to your privacy, Goldbar.net has agreed to disclose its information gathering and dissemination practices. Goldbar.net will notify you of:

What information is collected from you through the website  
The organization collecting the information  
How the information is used  
With whom the information may be shared  
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information  
The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under control  
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information  
If you feel that Goldbar.net is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you wish to modify information previously given, or have any questions regarding the privacy policy, please contact us via email at Support@ Goldbar.net or via postal mail at Goldbar Enterprises LLC, 6538 Collins Ave. #133, Miami Beach, FL 33141 or by telephone at (888) 594-0068 or +1(305) 671-3170.

MINORS

Goldbar.net does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Goldbar.net is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Goldbar.net collects information from our users at several different points on our website. For each visitor to the Goldbar.net site, our server automatically recognizes only the visitors domain name, but not the email address (where possible). Goldbar.net collects the email addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer (including survey information and site registrations). We use customer contact information to send the customer information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the customer when necessary. Your email address is never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used for verifying your name, address and other information, as well as to bill you for your use of our services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We may use information collected to promote other affiliate programs, products, websites and services. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by Goldbar.net and may be shared with third parties whose services are used for traffic analysis purposes. This information includes: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Website addresses. This information is used by Goldbar.net to maintain and improve the quality of the service and to generate statistics regarding use of the Goldbar.net site.

ACCESS OF INFORMATION

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to the information that we maintain about them, including financial information (e.g. credit card account information), unique identifier information (e.g. customer number or password), transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases), communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., emails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number). Users can access this information by contacting us via email at Support@ Goldbar.net or via postal mail at Goldbar Enterprises LLC, 6538 Collins Ave. #133, Miami Beach, FL 33141 or by telephone at (888) 594-0068 or +1(305) 671-3170.

SECURITY

Goldbar.net uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. We have taken appropriate measures within our physical facilities to help ensure the protection of your information from loss, misuse or alteration.

CHOICE/OPT-OUT

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners or to otherwise prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service or to otherwise prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected.

You can send email to Support@ Goldbar.net

You can send mail to the following postal address: Goldbar Enterprises LLC, 6538 Collins Ave. #133, Miami Beach, FL 33141.

You can call Goldbar at (888) 594-0068 or +1(305) 671-3170.

Please note that participation in certain activities on our website may be limited if personally identifiable information is not submitted for the user.

We, or a data provider we have engaged, may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads, content or services. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to these cookies. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to the registration data you have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to http://www.privacychoice.org/companies or http://aboutads.info/choices.

COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie for Goldbar.net, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site however without cookies the user may not have access to certain features on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart and record user-specific information on what pages Users access or visit.

Some of our business partners use cookies on their sites (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

LINKS

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Goldbar.net is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Goldbar.net.

DISCLOSURE

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Agreement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Site.

ACCOUNT ESTABLISHMENT

Upon sign up for our membership, Goldbar.net will send an email to the email address provided during registration. This is to establish that the new account is a valid account and your password will be delivered to you at this time. Accounts with invalid email addresses will not be able to participate in all features of Goldbar.net.

SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES

We will send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via email or telephone.

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so all users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If you are concerned about how your information is used, check the privacy policy periodically for modifications to the policy.
